<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Shayan Ali</title><description>A tiny letul human being, trying to code to make a living</description><link>https://your-website-url.com</link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 8 Nov 2023 17:37:42 +0100</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Wed, 8 Nov 2023 17:37:42 +0100</pubDate><ttl>250</ttl><atom:link href="https://your-website-url.com/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://your-website-url.com/posts/first-post</guid><title>Ethereum Merge: A historic event of human coordination</title><description>Ethereum blockchain is making its move to proof-of-stake from proof-of-work.</description><link>https://your-website-url.com/posts/first-post</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2022 15:21:00 +0200</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1>Ethereum Merge: A historic event of human coordination</h1><h2>What is Ethereum merge?</h2><p>Ethereum blockchain is making its move to proof-of-stake from proof-of-work.</p><h2>When it is happening?</h2><p>Around 15 September 2022 6 AM Eastern Time. (not confirmed)</p><h2>Why does anybody care about it?</h2><p>What does it mean for blockchain enthusiasts or why does anybody care about it? why are we even talking about it?. I think even if you are not into cryptocurrencies/NFTs and thinks that these things are just man-made artificial bubble waiting to get burst. Just think in an another perspective. This ethereum merge is like a historic event, not just for cryptocurrencies, but honestly broader, like for humans. It's a massive human historic event. Let's imagine that you work at Apple, And you want to do a major upgrade on the next iPhone. It's easy enough, right?. Tim Cook comes and says this is what we're going to do. People have to listen to him, there are conventional professional hierarchies and so on. ETH is decentralized, There's no boss. Ethereum network is maintained by a group of people from around the world where they work asynchronously, remotely, often times anonymously, we don't even know who these people are, and yet they're going to pull off this gigantic change to an open source ecosystem that's worth $200 billion just by coordinating. So it's absolutely a massive deal in the history of human coordination, I don't think we've ever had anything as large as this in a decentralized fashion as this.</p><h2>What do you need to do about it?</h2><p>Last thing to know, probably the most important thing to know. If you are sitting at home or wherever doing anything. What do you need to do about the merge? The good news is pretty much nothing. Just chill. Do not go crazy. Do not go start buying ETH on leverage just because your favorite crypto discord alpha group told you to do it. Do not start doing weird ETH farming stuff. Just relax, this is a big deal. No one knows exactly what's going to happen next. If you have ETH right now and you don't do anything, you will have ETH the next day after merge as well.</p><h2>Be Aware of Scams</h2><p>There will be a lot of scams going to happen in the next kind of few weeks around the merge before and after people saying like, oh, you have to do this in order to keep your ETH. Do not do anything and you will be fine. Just stay safe, get your popcorn out. Watch. It's a huge deal. It's going to be a lot of fun :)</p>]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>